extremereach.com 2019-07-03

# AdBridge privacy policy | Extreme Reach

### **Privacy Policy for **AdBridge (app.extremereach.com)****

Extreme Reach and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively “Extreme Reach” “our,” “we” or “us”) are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. 

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, disclose, store and otherwise process user information collected through Extreme Reach AdBridge. For information related to particular Services, please see the relevant policy posted on our Privacy website.

###### **Information We Collect**

Extreme Reach collects personal information about AdBridge users and user contacts. This information is collected when users register, update their user profiles, or add contacts to their AdBridge account.

Depending on the services Extreme Reach provides to you, we may also collect information about your ads and campaigns, and the ads themselves.  For information regarding Privacy related to your particular services, please see [https://extremereach.com/privacy-policy/](https://extremereach.com/privacy-policy/)

###### **How Collected Data Is Used**

Extreme Reach uses personal information about AdBridge users and contacts to process orders, deliveries, or other transactions users conduct using the AdBridge platform. We may also use information to manage the application, track usage, and improve the application services. 

We may also use this information to recommend products and services that might be of interest to you, to send you marketing and advertising messages such as newsletters, announcements, or special offers or to notify you about our upcoming events. We may also use such information to provide you products and services, such as to fulfill your requests for products or to help us personalize our offerings to you. We also use your personal information to support our business functions, such as fraud prevention or legal functions. 

Other non-personally identifiable information that we collect is used to manage ads and campaigns.

We use your data only for the purposes described by our privacy policies.

###### **Information Disclosed to Outside Parties**

Information, including personal contact information, from orders, deliveries, and other business transactions may be disclosed to the third parties (i.e., your employer and their business partners) involved in those transactions. 

Extreme Reach may also disclose personal information to our third-party vendors and service providers that work with us. We will only share personal information to these vendors and service providers to help us provide a product or service to you.

We do not otherwise sell, trade, or transfer collected information to outside parties, unless we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

###### **How We Protect Your Information**

Security of all information is of the utmost importance for Extreme Reach. We use technical and physical safeguards to protect the security of your information from unauthorized disclosure. We also make all attempts to ensure that only necessary people and third parties have access to personal and confidential information.

We require that our third party service providers (1) use confidential information only to perform their obligations, and (2) otherwise maintain the confidentiality of such information. These third party service providers and channel partners are expected to maintain privacy and security protections that are consistent with Extreme Reach’s privacy and information security policies.

###### **Transparency and Choice**

Some web browsers (including some mobile web browsers) provide settings that allow you to control or reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer, tablet or mobile device. Although you are not required to accept cookies, if you block or reject them, you may not be able to use an auto-log-on feature. For more information, visit the help page for your web browser.

###### **GDPR**

Extreme Reach is committed to protecting your data in compliance with the  General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). Extreme Reach is the processor or controller of data collected from our AdBridge platform. Our Data Privacy Officer can be contacted at privacy@extremereach.com.

Should you have any issues with how we handle your data, we request that you contact us first so that we can make every effort to address your concerns. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

The legal basis for collecting and processing your data is “legitimate interest” based on the need for basic user information regarding those individuals using our services. We store and process data in the United States.

###### **International Transfers**

We do not transfer any of your information submitted via AdBridge across international borders.  We store data in the United States and process data in the United States, Canada and the UK, depending on customer location. AdBridge data accessed by customers internationally may be transferred by such customers.

###### **Children**

Extreme Reach recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy and safety of children. Our website and services are primarily directed towards the advertising industry and are not directed towards children. We do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13.

###### **Data Retention**

We retain data we collect from AdBridge profiles to support AdBridge transactions. We may be obligated to retain this data to support contractual or regulatory reasons. 

###### **Changes to This Policy**

Extreme Reach reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice (except for EU subjects, where we will notify you if we change how we process your data and will obtain your consent for alternate use of your data). Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised version on our website.

###### **Opt-out**

You can opt-out of marketing emails by contacting Extreme Reach or by clicking the unsubscribe link from a marketing email, which will remove you from our marketing list. 

For information on options for cookies see the Transparency and Choice section above.

###### **Contact Information**

You can contact privacy@extremereach.com for requests related to rights of erasure, correction, restriction of processing, and portability.

_last updated: December 18, 2018 to make language consistent with our other privacy policies. No changes to how we process data have been made._
